I'm going to eat it.
Thank you for the meal.
We are at the office in Tokyo.
This is our company.
We are finally going to be in the
video.
It's very fulfilling.
Today's video is not about this office.
As usual, we are going to introduce you
to the office.
Recently, many adults have been coming
to Tokyo.
And they are worried about the cost of
staying in the office.
So, we are going to introduce you to
the office.
It's a big office.
Is it a YouTube apartment?
I think so.
We are going to have a meeting about
the payment.
I can't.
I'll pay 90% of the cost.
OK.
She is cute.
I haven't rented the office yet.
But, I found a good place.
What?
Is it a good place?
I asked her to rent the office.
She lent me the key.
But, I thought it was good to have a
big space.
It costs about 300,000 yen.
It's expensive.
What do you mean?
You rent the office and pay 300,000
yen?
Yes.
You pay 300,000 yen for rent.
But, it's very cheap.
Please subscribe to this channel.
The person who lent me the key said,
I'm not going, so please be careful.
What do you mean?
I'm sorry.
So, I was given only the key.
What is that?
Is it a gift certificate?
It wasn't explained in particular, but
it's like,
Please feel free to see the inside.
No!
If the market price is cheap, it's a
gift certificate.
It's a gift certificate.
But if it's a gift certificate, you'll
be told.
I'm not going.
It wasn't explained in detail, but the
person who lent me the key said,
I'm not going, so please be careful.
No!
I don't want to go.
Suddenly, it's like a love affair.
Love affair?
What?
Let's go.
First of all, please bring a weapon.
Please bring a gift certificate.
It's not a self-proclaimed property
yet.
You just made a subtle face.
It's a subtle face, or is it really a
gift certificate?
When they jump, we all go,
Let's jump.
What are you going to do?
We are going to jump.
Ready, go!
Jump!
We made it!
It was a long journey.
We made it.
The beautiful thing behind us.
Beautiful?
It's like...
QLDK.
It's big.
It's QLDK.
It's a single building.
It's big.
It was cheap.
I'm not going there, but you can watch
it.
What is that?
It's a royal palace.
You can explain it.
I should have said it earlier.
We haven't moved in yet.
I don't think we can turn on the light.
We should have done it in the morning.
It's summer.
Why did we do it at night?
We had a lot of things to do.
We were busy.
We only have time for today.
Let's take a look.
It's like a palace.
Is it open?
It's interesting.
It's dark.
It's true.
It's a leader.
It's okay.
Let's go.
Please subscribe to our channel.
lol
It's painful.
Are you okayens from the pain of
feeling?
I'm fine!
End of review
Thank you so much!
I'm going to go to the front room one
by one.
It's written here.
Maybe it's a jane's.
It's a jane's dressing room.
What kind of nano nano?
It's a very good room.
I'll go in.
Do you have a VT?
I'm going in.
Excuse me.
It's a hotel.
There is a door.
It's a jane's.
What is this?
I was surprised.
Why do you have such a curiosity?
It's a real one.
Let's do our best together.
Why?
We haven't borrowed it yet.
I'm going to break it.
I can't close it.
What?
What is this?
I'm going to break it.
I can't close it.
I'm scared.
I'm really scared.
I heard it.
I'm scared.
She is crying.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Are you OK?
I'm going to do it in Japanese.
I'm sorry.
Rock-paper-scissors.
Wait.
I'm going to use my eyes.
Rock-paper-scissors.
Kaya is the winner.
I can't do it.
You are the oldest.
This is a big sword.
What is it?
It looks like a sword.
It's a room for Kana.
It might be a room for Kana.
Wait.
I have a dancer.
I'm going to dance.
Kaya is amazing.
What are you doing?
What did you get?
It's a doraemon.
Enjoy it.
Let's play together.
I'm scared.
It's my room.
It's decided.
What?
It's a toilet.
It's my room.
It's decided.
It's beautiful.
Is this room cleaned by the owner?
It's the best.
Then, you can play the guitar here.
Is it okay?
It's cool.
I'm going to buy a room for Waka.
It's decided.
To be continued.
I'm going to go to the room.
Let's go.
Yuna, open it.
What's this?
What's going on?
There's Wi-Fi.
That's a lot of money.
There's Wi-Fi even though there's no
electricity.
It's a room with a wall and a door.
It's a walk-in closet.
Wait, the clothes are here.
The clothes are here.
I went to the office and found a lot of
clothes.
This is a wardrobe.
There are a lot of clothes in this
room.
It's a room with a lot of clothes.
I'll take this room.
I'll open it.
It's a second floor.
It's huge.
I'm going to go to the bathroom.
Screams
What's up guys....
I'm so upset
She's wearingундress
Oh so shock
Why are you wearing such intoxicating s
badge
That's hurtful
I taking a good pictures
Oi
I'm not good at this.
Let's move on to the next room.
Don't pretend you didn't see it.
Next, the room of the last room.
Vitamin C.
I can't decide which one to choose.
It's so dark.
It's dark.
It's quite dark.
I'm scared.
Is it a bad idea to turn back?
It's a mirror.
This house has a lot of storage.
We can put clothes in the closet.
We have a lot of air conditioners.
Which one do you want?
Let's look at this room first.
Let's look at the right room.
We have the same room as we have seen
so far.
It's quite big.
We have the same room.
We have a lot of rooms like this.
All of them are big.
All of them have storage.
Next, this room.
It's a bit obvious.
It's a bath.
It's a washroom.
It's a new bath.
It's beautiful.
It's not that old.
It's a renovation.
The washroom is beautiful.
We can fit four people in this room.
The bath is good.
It's L.
It's R.
It's not L.
It's L.
Let's go!
It's spacious!
There is a Japanese-style room.
It's very spacious.
Why is there a whiteboard?
You can do a night view.
What?
The electricity is on in winter.
Look at this. The color is different.
Match the color.
The room is ready.
Wow!
I haven't borrowed it yet, but I'm
going to borrow it soon.
Do you really pay 300,000 yen?
I don't pay 300,000 yen.
I didn't know that.
I don't know if we'll pay it.
I'm not sure if I'll pay it.
You're not being pulled from your
salary, are you?
I'm not sure.
I'm not sure if I can do it.
I'm going to change the topic.
What?
I'm not sure if I can do it.
I'm going to ask you.
I want to name it like a house.
I like this name.
There is no such thing as a QLD.
QD doesn't need to be big.
So I want to name it like this.
If you have any complaints, please tell
us.
I have a complaint.
I'm going to change the topic.
Yagata.
Inari-hara is a very popular place.
I think so.
Yagata.
It's a suspicious place.
It's a house of oil.
Yeiei.
I like it.
It's cute.
I want to go inside.
It's warm.
Today is Yeiei.
I'm going to go inside.
OK.
I'll give you a hint.
Choose one.
Yagata or Yeiei.
OK.
Please subscribe to this channel.
What is it?
Can you look down at the end and raise
your hand if you think it's okay?
I don't want to stay here every time.
Not a hotel?
The hotel will be gone.
If you don't want to stay here, can you
go back to the hotel?
I'll decide that now.
Outside?
I don't have a choice.
I'm worried.
Can you do that?
Yes.
Can you look up at the end and raise
your hand if you think it's okay?
I don't know.
Please subscribe to this channel.
I'm not sure.
How is it?
What do you think?
We'll announce the result after the
video is uploaded.
No way!
But I don't know where to stay.
I'll stay at the next time.
I'll be handed a sleeping bag.
We've got the result.
I'm looking forward to it.
If you rent a sleeping bag, you can
stay at the next time.
Bye!
That was pretty sad.
We are still preparing for the next
video.
We can't show you the room yet.
You should have told us that earlier.
It was cheap, so we don't know if you
are going to be surprised.
It's white.
It's like a gorilla.
We are going to clean up the room.
Maybe we are going to clean up the room
together next time.
That's right.
That's all for today.
Thank you for watching.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Please like the video.
Bye bye.